Now let's go ahead and deploy this to With the Rinkeby test net,
现在让我们把它部署到 Rinkeby 测试网上
and what do we need to deploy this to the Rinkeby test net?
那么部署到 Rinkeby 测试网上需要做哪些事呢？
Well, let's jump into our hard hat config first.
让我们先转到 "hardhat.config"
And let's clean this up, we don't really need this accounts task,
并且清除掉这些内容，我们并不需要这个 "accounts" task
so I'm just going to delete it,
所以我们要把它删掉
I don't really need this comment. So I'm going to delete this too.
我也不需要这个注释了，所以也要删掉
And let's jump into the network section,
现在让我们进入 "network" 部分
we're not going to be working with ropsten. So we're gonna go ahead and dump that.
我们不会使用 "ropsten"，所以我们扔掉它
We are however, going to be working with rink B, the URL is going to be that same Rinkeby RPC URL.
但我们要使用 "Rinkeby"，"url" 还是一样的 `RINKEBY_RPC_URL`
So we're going to define that up here, like we did before.
我们在这里定义它，就和之前的做法一样
And if you want to copy paste from your last project, feel free to do so
你可以选择从上一个项目中直接复制粘贴过来
you can also follow along with me or fastforward me
也可以选择跟着我或者快进
the counts is going to be the same.
`accounts` 是相同的
I'm going to go ahead and just copy paste the gas reporter with what we had from before.
我这里直接复制粘贴了之前使用过的 `gasReporter`
So we're going to add this
所以我们要添加一句
constant corn market cap API key equals process dot EMV dot corn market cap API key.
`const COINMARKETCAP_API_KEY = process.env.COINMARKETCAP_API_KEY`
Do the same thing with the ether scan API key Licious add everything in here. Now.
`ETHERSCAN_API_KEY` 也是一样的，添加到这里来
We have our ether scan section in here already,
我们已经准备好了 `etherscan` 部分
we're gonna have our gas reporter be false,
我们让 `gasReporter` 保持为 `false`
because I don't really feel like using it right now.
因为我现在用不到它
And then finally, we're going to add one more thing in here.
最后，我们还要再添加一个东西
Remember how in our last project,
还记得我们在上一个项目中
before we actually verified we waited some block confirmations.
在实际验证之前，我们等待了一些区块的确认
That way ether scan could make sure to catch up.
这样 `etherscan` 就可以保证能跟上进度
Well, we can do the exact same thing in here
这里，我们可以执行一些相同的操作
in our hard hat dot config,
在我们的 "hardhat.config" 中
we can add a section for each test net for how many blocks we want to wait,
我们可以为每个测试网添加一部分，告诉它我们想等待多少区块
I'm going to add block confirmations of six.
我将添加为 `blockConfirmations: 6`
Now back on our deploy Funmi.
现在，回到我们的 "deploy-fund-me"
In a new section, I can add wait confirmations of network dot config. That block on for motions, or one
在新的部分中，我可以添加 `waitConfirmations: network.config.blockConfirmations || 1`
is or one means if no block confirmations is given in our Hardhead dot config
这个 `|| 1` 表示，如果在 "hardhat.config" 中没有指定 `blockConfirmations`
will just wait for one block.
我们就只等待一个区块
And again, the reason we want to wait for approximately six block confirmations
再回顾一下，我们之所以要等待大约 6 个区块确认
is we want to give ether scan a chance to index our transaction.
是因为我们想给 "etherscan" 一个索引我们交易的机会
And I added a chain ID 42 when it should be for my mistake.
我把这里的 `chainId` 应该是 4 而不是 42，我的错
And of course, we're going to need our dot env file, where we add all of our stuff from the last session,
当然，我们还需要 ".env" 文件，其中添加了上次会话的所有内容
the RIP ERP CRL private key ether scan API and then coin market cap API.
有 "RINKEBY_RPC_URL" "PRIVATE_KEY" "ETHERSCAN_API(_KEY)" 以及 "COINMARKETCAP_API(_KEY)"
All right moment of truth. Let's try this out.
好了，关键时刻到了，让我们来试一试
If we run yarn Hardhead deploy dash dash network Rinkeby.
如果我们运行 `yarn hardhat deploy --network rinkeby`
It should not deploy any marks because we have this if statement in our mock deployment.
它应该不会部署任何 "mocks"，因为我们在 "mock" 的部署中有这个 `if` 语句
But it should deploy our Funmi contract using the correct price feed address.
但它应该会部署我们的 `FundMe` 合约并使用正确的喂价地址
And then it'll go ahead and verify it.
接着它会对其进行验证
Since we're waiting for six block confirmations,
由于我们等待了 6 个区块的确认
we can even be super secure by adding dash dash tags and just running the funding tag.
所以我们甚至可以通过添加 `--tags` 来确保安全，只需要运行 `fundme` 标签
But we're just going to do yarn hearted deploy network Rigby.
但这里我们只运行 `yarn hardhat deploy --network rinkeby`
And let's see what happens.
让我们看看会发生什么
All right, and we're deploying funding. And we can see the transaction that we have for fun me,
好的，我们正在部署 "FundMe"，并且可以看到我们拥有一个关于 "FundMe" 的交易
this is that logging feature, we have log is true for deploying Funmi.
这就是日志功能，因为 `deploy("FundMe")` 这里的 `log` 为 `true`
So it gives us the transaction once it has a transaction,
所以一旦有了交易它就会提供给我们这个交易
and it will give us the address once we have the address.
一旦有了地址它也会将地址提供给我们
So we're going to wait six block confirmations for this transaction to finish going through.
现在我们要等待 6 个区块确认以完成这笔交易
Now we see we've deployed this contract address with X amount of gas.
现在我们已经看到了部署好的合约地址，它使用了这么多的 gas
And now we're running the verification process.
现在我们正在运行验证过程
While the verification process is running,
在验证过程正在运行的时候
we can pull up Rinkeby ether scan,
我们可以打开 "rinkeby etherscan"
paste our address in here and see that we have indeed created this contract.
把我们的地址粘贴到这里，可以看到我们确实已经创建了这个合约
And now it looks like we've successfully verified the contract on ether scan.
看起来我们已经成功在 "etherscan" 上验证了我们的合约
So if we hit refresh, we can indeed see that the contract has been verified. Awesome.
如果我们点击刷新，就可以看到合约确实已经被验证了，非常好
All right. So this is fantastic.
太好了，非常棒
Our deploy script is looking great,
我们的部署脚本看起来非常棒
we're able to deploy to a local chain, we're able to deploy to a test that
现在我们能够部署到本地链，还可以部署到测试网络
and if we wanted to, we could deploy to any network that we wanted
如果我们想的话，我们可以部署到任何我们想要的网络上
simply by updating our hard hat config,
只需要更新我们的 "hardhat.config"
and then updating our helper config.
然后更新我们的 "helper(-hardhat)-config"
This is fantastic. Great work so far.
目前为止，干得漂亮